hypefortype.com 2010-12-12

# HypeForType Buy Fonts, Try Fonts, Exclusive Faces - Privacy Policy

**Online Privacy Policy**

By accessing or using this website, you agree to the terms of the HypeForType Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you don't agree to these terms, please don't use the site. HypeForType reserves the right to change this policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the policy at the time of such use.

**The Collection of Personal Information**

When you engage in certain activities on this site, like viewing prices, ordering or selecting products, using HypeForType downloading software, or entering contests - we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form.

It's entirely optional for you to engage in these activities and therefore provide this information. If you do chose to provide it, we will treat it in the strictest confidence and in accordance with the data protection act, and will only use it for the purposes stated. We don't share your data with any other parties, and will only have access to your name and email address for contact purposes as the remaining information is held in our secure database. Currently all transacts are carried out via Paypal, so we will have no access to your credit or debit card details at any time.

**How Your Personal Information Is Used**

HypeForType collects your information in order to record and support your effective use of this site. If you order a product that is to be electronically downloaded, for example, the information may at a later date be used to verify credit cards. Currently the information verified will be to issue multi-user license documents, re-deliver orders in the case of transmission failure and to maintain your customer history. We don't use your details for anything else, or give them to anyone else either.

**Protection of Your Personal Information**

The personal information that you provide is protected in several ways. Access by you to your personal information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. In addition, your personal information resides on a secure server that only selected HypeForType personnel may access via password. HypeForType currently uses Paypal for payment processing, which is a fully secure business transaction service so you have full security and peace of mind.
